(Sheldon:)...I've co-authored two papers
in notable peer-reviewed journals...
(Sheldon:)...and I'm close to figuring out
why the Large Hadron Collider...
(Sheldon:)...has yet to isolate
the Higgs boson particle.
(Leonard:)You left out, got chafed testicles
because you no longer wear underpants.
(Sheldon:)The dice giveth
and the dice taketh away.
- ls Raj out with Emily again?
- Yeah. Every night for the last month.
Wow. I can't believe he has a girIfriend.
(Sheldon(rolls dice):)Me neither.
(Howard:)Here's some other fun news
on the Raj-Emily front.
(Howard:)He gave her a pair of diamond earrings
and leased her a car.
(Penny:)You're kidding.
(Leonard:)- Think she's taking advantage of him?
- Oh, of course not.
(Penny:)She wouldn't do something like that.
She's deaf.
(Leonard:)Deaf women can't be gold diggers?
(Penny:)Handicapped people are nice, Leonard.
Everyone knows that.
(Sheldon:)I actually have information about Raj that
would be helpful with this discussion.